

Eric Li (艾瑞克 李)

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER & AI ENGINEER

Details

Hong Kong

Phone: +18596674314

Mail: ericlee.apollo@gmail.com

Telegram: @ericleetele

<u>LinkedIn:</u>

linkedin.com/in/ericlee7777

Skills

Fast Learner

Hard worker

Computer Skills

Team Player

Excellent Communication Skills

Leadership and Teamwork

Good time management skills

Always on time

Flexible schedule

React

Solidity

AI / ML / NLP

Javascript

Rust

Ruby on Rails

Profile

Passionate Full Stack & Blockchain Developer offering 8+ years of relevant experience in Blockchain, ML and Robotic.

I have experience developing DeFi, DEX, DApp, Trading Bot, Token, autonomous systems and artificial intelligence.

I am fluent in Solidity, Web3.js, Python and JavaScript ,and have worked on a variety of projects as a consultant, helping clients achieve their goals.

I am also keen on several JavaScript and Python web frameworks like Vue, React, Django and Flask.

I am a life-long learner and is looking forward to working on exciting and challenging projects.

I am continuously trying to improve, learn more and gain new experiences. With a strong attention to detail and accuracy and the important ability to function well in a team setting.

Looking for a Blockchain Developer job within a forward-moving company.

Employment History

Senior Blockchain Developer at Jaarivs, Hong Kong

JANUARY 2018 — DECEMBER 2021

- NFT marketplace with Smart UI and high-end functionalities in Ethereum, Binance, Cardano, Solana, Polygon, etc
- DEX and Centralized Crypto Exchange
- Trading bot with strong strategies (Front running, snipping, arbitrage, contract bot)
- Advanced Trading Platform (Stocks, CFD, Forex, Option, Features...)
- · Portfolio Tracking Platform
- · Multichain Web and Mobile Wallet
- Crypto Betting and Casino
- Yield Farming Protocols
- Automated Market Making (AMM) protocols
- Flash Loans
- Impermanent loss, governance tokens
- · P2P/Pool Lending and Borrowing
- Crypto Collectible Platforms and Non-Fungible Tokens
- Custom dApps
- NFT Game Development
- ERC20, ERC777, ERC721, ERC1155 Smart Contract Development
- Token Design Stable Coins, Utility, Security, Investment, Dividend coins
- Blockchain network launching by using C++, Golang
- Fixing and changing Zero Layer(Cosmos)

Al Engineer & Blockchain Developer at Jaarivs, Hong Kong

DECEMBER 2016 — JANUARY 2018

- Designed and implemented NLU data, dialog stories, rules, forms, and custom actions (Python) for industry-relevant demonstrator chat-bots.
- Extended Rasa Open Source (Python) available at
 https://github.com/rasaHQ/rasa. This is an open-source machine learning
 framework to automate text and voice based conversations: NLU, dialogue
 management, connect to Slack, Facebook, and more

AWS

Languages

English

Chinese

Hobbies

Market Researching, Gaming, Sports

- Implemented Python Asyncio in Back-End APIs resulting in dramatically improved throughput rates
- Created CI/CD pipeline that trains a Rasa bot, builds a custom docker image, stores the artifacts in AWS S3 and AWS ECR, automatically creates an AWS EKS cluster using the eksctl CLI, deploys Rasa with Helm, and Smoke Tests using Python
- Developed ML models for NLP, including methods for domain adaptation, methods for automated feature selection, methods for optimization of Fmeasure. Applied models such as logistic regression, SVM, CRF for both classification and sequence tagging
- · VZN, LSD token deployed on Binance, Ethereum, Polygon, Cronos, Solana
- · Multichain DEX website UX/UI design and development
- · Presale and IDO contracts
- Crosschain (10 chains such as Binance, Ethereum, Polygon, Cronos and etc)
 bridge smart contracts
- Crosschain Swap/Liquidity/Farming/Staking smart contracts
- Crosschain NFT Marketplace (Genesis NFT)
- Crosschain NFT Game(Genesis NFT)

Intern at Jaarivs, Hong Kong

AUGUST 2016 — DECEMBER 2016

- Front-End Development
 - Worked on Trello to fix feedbacks and issues list and made report
 - React.js, Next.js, Vue.js Frameworks for Dapp, Defi, Dex and NFT websites
 - Web3.js Integration
- Back-End Development
 - Worked on AWS EC2, S3 bucket and Azure
 - Node.js Back-End framework for websites
 - MySQL, MongoDB, PostgreSQL database for website DB
- Customer Support
 - Received and listed up customers advice and opinions
 - Making daily report for referring to make schedule of development of team
 - Replying to customers' messages by call for SMS

Education

Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science, The University of Hong Kong, Hong Kong

APRIL 2012 — MARCH 2016